Guide to the W.F. Mai papers, 1955-1993.
Mai, W.F. papers, 1955-1993.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
W.F. Mai papers, 1955-1993.
21-29-3304
W.F. Mai
.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, meeting minutes, bibliographic information, and photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, meeting minutes, bibliographic information, and photographs relating to Dr. Mai's forty-four years in Plant Pathology at Cornell University and his work on the Archives Committee of the Society of Nematologists.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Plant Pathology, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, meeting minutes, bibliographic information, and photographs relating to Dr. Mai's forty-four years in Plant Pathology at Cornell University and his work on the Archives Committee of the Society of Nematologists.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Mai, W.F.; Cornell University--Faculty.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.; Society of Nematologists.
Subjects:
Plant pathology--study and teaching.; Plant pathologists.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Photographs
  - Bill Mai (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Staff, Faculty, Visitors (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Personnel-Research lab, VN lab, L.I. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sports Teams (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Meetings, Workshops, and Conferences (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nematology (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Plant Science Building (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Courses (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Charts and Instructional Photos (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Campus Scenes (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Series II. Subject Files
  - Plant Nematology Workshop--1, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Plant Nematology Workshop--2, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mai-Awards, Articles, Recognition (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NSF Grant-Nematology, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Book-Pictorial Key to Genera, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Society of Nematologists-Archives Committee--1, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Society of Nemotologists-Archives Committee--2, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Nemisys International Project Update, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Plant Pathology Department (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Plant Pathology-Academic Personnel, 1983-1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Plant Pathology Faculty Meeting Minutes, Aug. 1, 1993-Dec. 2, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Microbial Germplasm Data Net, Oct. 1989, Nov. 1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Nemanet-Ohio State University Nematode Database Information, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Paper-"Current Status of Maize White Line Mosaic", NECIC, Bouthroyd, Zitter and Lyons, Feb. 12-13, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Fundamentals of Plant Pathology Manuscript Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Series III. Publications
  - Pflanzenschutz Nachrichten-The Concepts of Etiology in the History of Plant Pathology, Bayer, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Abstracts of Theses-Cornell University, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Pictorial Key to Genera of Plant Parasitic Nematodes, W.F. Mai, H.H. Lyon, 1962 (Box 1)